<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lewis R Elliott</title>
    <link>https://lewis-r-elliott.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Lewis R Elliott</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lewis-r-elliott.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://lewis-r-elliott.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lewis-r-elliott.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I am currently a Lecturer in Environment and Public Health at the European Centre for Environment and Human Health at the University of Exeter, UK.
Research My research primarily concerns the benefits that the natural environment has on human physical health and psychological well-being. I primarily use quantitative methods and the analysis of large surveys in my work, though I have experience of experimental and intervention research as well. I am currently co-I on a number of research projects including GroundsWell, Smartline, and What does blue do for you?</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;I am currently a Lecturer in Environment and Public Health at the &lt;a href=&#34;ecehh.org&#34;&gt;European Centre for Environment and Human Health&lt;/a&gt; at the University of Exeter, UK.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;research&#34;&gt;Research&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My research primarily concerns the benefits that the natural environment has on human physical health and psychological well-being. I primarily use quantitative methods and the analysis of large surveys in my work, though I have experience of experimental and intervention research as well. I am currently co-I on a number of research projects including &lt;a href=&#34;https://ukprp.org/what-we-fund/groundswell/&#34;&gt;GroundsWell&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.smartline.org.uk/&#34;&gt;Smartline&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.york.ac.uk/healthsciences/closing-the-gap/funded-projects/&#34;&gt;What does blue do for you?&lt;/a&gt;. I previously worked extensively as a post-doc on the EU Horizon 2020 funded &lt;a href=&#34;bluehealth2020.eu&#34;&gt;BlueHealth&lt;/a&gt; project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;teaching&#34;&gt;Teaching&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As for teaching, I lead a module on &lt;a href=&#34;https://medicine.exeter.ac.uk/people/module/?mod_code=HPDM029&#34;&gt;Nature, Health, and Well-being&lt;/a&gt; for the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.exeter.ac.uk/postgraduate/courses/medicine/environment-health-msc/&#34;&gt;MSc Environment and Human Health&lt;/a&gt; where I also lecture on quantitative methods and statistics. I co-convene a &lt;a href=&#34;https://medicine.exeter.ac.uk/cpd/naturehealth/&#34;&gt;CPD course&lt;/a&gt; on the same topic. I also lecture or lead research groups for the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.exeter.ac.uk/undergraduate/courses/medicine/medicine/&#34;&gt;BMBS&lt;/a&gt; programme, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.exeter.ac.uk/undergraduate/courses/medicalsci/medicalsci/&#34;&gt;BSc Medical Sciences&lt;/a&gt;, and for a module on &lt;a href=&#34;https://medicine.exeter.ac.uk/programmes/programme/modules/module/?moduleCode=CSC2010M&amp;amp;ay=2018/9&#34;&gt;Oceans and Human Health&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Journal publications</title>
      <link>https://lewis-r-elliott.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lewis-r-elliott.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>2021 2020 2019 2018 2017 2016 2015
2021   van den Bogerd, N., Elliott, L. R., White, M. P., Mishra, H. S., Bell, S., Porter, M., Sydenham, Z., Garrett, J. K., &amp;amp; Fleming, L. E. (2021). Urban blue space renovation and local resident and visitor well-being: A case study from Plymouth, UK. Landscape and Urban Planning, 215, 104232. https://doi.org/10.1016/j.landurbplan.2021.104232
  Menneer, T., Qi, Z., Taylor, T., Paterson, C., Tu, G.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://lewis-r-elliott.github.io/publications/#2021&#34;&gt;2021&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://lewis-r-elliott.github.io/publications/#2020&#34;&gt;2020&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://lewis-r-elliott.github.io/publications/#2019&#34;&gt;2019&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://lewis-r-elliott.github.io/publications/#2018&#34;&gt;2018&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://lewis-r-elliott.github.io/publications/#2017&#34;&gt;2017&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://lewis-r-elliott.github.io/publications/#2016&#34;&gt;2016&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://lewis-r-elliott.github.io/publications/#2015&#34;&gt;2015&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;2021&#34;&gt;2021&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;van den Bogerd, N., Elliott, L. R., White, M. P., Mishra, H. S., Bell, S., Porter, M., Sydenham, Z., Garrett, J. K., &amp;amp; Fleming, L. E. (2021). Urban blue space renovation and local resident and visitor well-being: A case study from Plymouth, UK. Landscape and Urban Planning, 215, 104232. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.landurbplan.2021.104232&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.landurbplan.2021.104232&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Menneer, T., Qi, Z., Taylor, T., Paterson, C., Tu, G., Elliott, L. R., Morrissey, K., &amp;amp; Mueller, M. (2021). Changes in Domestic Energy and Water Usage during the UK COVID-19 Lockdown Using High-Resolution Temporal Data. International Journal of Environmental Research and Public Health, 18(13), 6818. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.3390/ijerph18136818&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.3390/ijerph18136818&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;White, M. P., Elliott, L. R., Grellier, J., Economou, T., Bell, S., Bratman, G. N., Cirach, M., Gascon, M., Lima, M. L., Lõhmus, M., Nieuwenhuijsen, M., Ojala, A., Roiko, A., Schultz, P. W., van den Bosch, M., &amp;amp; Fleming, L. E. (2021). Associations between green/blue spaces and mental health across 18 countries. Scientific Reports, 11(1), 8903. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1038/s41598-021-87675-0&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1038/s41598-021-87675-0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Börger, T., Campbell, D., White, M. P., Elliott, L. R., Fleming, L. E., Garrett, J. K., Hattam, C., Hynes, S., Lankia, T., &amp;amp; Taylor, T. (2021). The value of blue-space recreation and perceived water quality across Europe: A contingent behaviour study. Science of the Total Environment, 145597. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.scitotenv.2021.145597&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.scitotenv.2021.145597&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Adade, E.A, Elliott, L.R., Fleming, L.E., &amp;amp; Wuijts, S. (2021). Governance strategies to promote health and well-being:  urban blue space infrastructure initiatives in Plymouth (UK). International Journal of Urban Sustainable Development. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1080/19463138.2021.1885038&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1080/19463138.2021.1885038&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lambert, J. D., Elliott, L. R., Taylor, A. H., Farrand, P., Haase, A. M., &amp;amp; Greaves, C. J. (2021). A novel method for assessing design fidelity in web-based behavioral interventions. Health Psychology, 40(3), 217-225. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1037/hea0001046&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1037/hea0001046&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;2020&#34;&gt;2020&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Elliott, L. R., White, M. P., Fleming, L. E., Abraham, C., &amp;amp; Taylor, A. H. (2020). Redesigning walking brochures using behaviour change theory: Implications for walking intentions in natural environments, daaa150, Health Promotion International. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1093/heapro/daaa150&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1093/heapro/daaa150&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tester-Jones, M., White, M. P., Elliott, L. R., Weinstein, N., Grellier, J., Economou, T., Bratman, G. N., Gascon, M., Korpela, K. M., Lima, M. L., Nieuwenhuijsen, M., O’Connor, A., Ojala, A., Roiko, A., van den Bosch, M. A.,  &amp;amp; Fleming, L. E. (2020). Experiences of nature for people with common mental health disorders: Results from an 18 country cross-sectional study. Scientific Reports. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1038/s41598-020-75825-9&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1038/s41598-020-75825-9&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;White, M. P., Bratman, G. N., Pahl, S., Young, G., Cracknell, D., &amp;amp; Elliott, L. R. (2020). Affective reactions to losses and gains in biodiversity: Testing a prospect theory approach. Journal of Environmental Psychology, 72, 101502. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.jenvp.2020.101502&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.jenvp.2020.101502&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;White, M. P., Elliott, L. R., Gascon, M., Roberts, B., &amp;amp; Fleming, L. E. (2020). Blue space, health and well-being: A narrative overview and synthesis of potential benefits. Environmental Research, 191, 110169. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.envres.2020.110169&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.envres.2020.110169&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Garrett, J. K., White, M. P., Elliott, L. R., Wheeler, B. W., &amp;amp; Fleming, L. E. (2020). Urban nature and physical activity: Investigating associations using self-reported and accelerometer data and the role of household income. Environmental Research, 190, 109899. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.envres.2020.109899&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.envres.2020.109899&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vert, C., Gascón, M., Ranzani, O., Márquez, S., Triguero-Mas, M., Carrasco-Turigas, G., Arjona, L., Koch, S., Llopis, M., Donaire-Gonzalez, D., Elliott, L. R., &amp;amp; Nieuwenhuijsen, M. (2020). Physical and mental health effects of repeated short walks in a blue space environment: a randomised crossover study. Environmental Research, 188, 109812. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.envres.2020.109812&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.envres.2020.109812&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bell, S., Mishra, H. S., Elliott, L. R., Shellock, R., Vassiljev, P., Porter, M., Sydenham, Z., &amp;amp; White, M. P. (2020). Urban Blue Acupuncture: A Protocol for Evaluating a Complex Landscape Design Intervention to Improve Health and Wellbeing in a Coastal Community. Sustainability, 12(10), 4084. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.3390/su12104084&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.3390/su12104084&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Elliott, L. R., White, M. P., Grellier, J., Garrett, J. K., Cirach, M., Wheeler, B. W., Bratman, G. N., van den Bosch, M. A., Ojala, A., Roiko, A., Lima, M. L., O’Connor, A., Gascon, M., Nieuwenhuijsen, M., &amp;amp; Fleming, L. E. (2020). Research Note: Residential distance and recreational visits to coastal and inland blue spaces in eighteen countries. Landscape and Urban Planning, 198, 103800. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.landurbplan.2020.103800&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.landurbplan.2020.103800&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hooyberg, A., Roose, H., Grellier, J., Elliott, L. R., Lonneville, B., White, M. P., Michels, N., De Henauw, S., Vandegehuchte, M., &amp;amp; Everaert, G. (2020). General health and residential proximity to the coast in Belgium: Results from a cross-sectional health survey. Environmental Research, 184, 109225. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.envres.2020.109225&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.envres.2020.109225&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;2019&#34;&gt;2019&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeo, N. L., Elliott, L. R., Bethel, A., White, M. P., Dean, S. G., &amp;amp; Garside, R. (2019). Indoor nature interventions for health and wellbeing of older adults in residential settings: a systematic review. The Gerontologist. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1093/geront/gnz019&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1093/geront/gnz019&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pasanen, T. P., White, M. P., Wheeler, B. W., Garrett, J. K., &amp;amp; Elliott, L. R. (2019). Neighbourhood blue space, health and wellbeing: The mediating role of different types of physical activity. Environment International, 131, 105016. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.envint.2019.105016&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.envint.2019.105016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vert, C., Carrasco-Turigas, G., Zijlema, W., Espinosa, A., Cano-Riu, L., Elliott, L. R., … Gascon, M. (2019). Impact of a riverside accessibility intervention on use, physical activity, and wellbeing: A mixed methods pre-post evaluation. Landscape and Urban Planning, 190, 103611. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.landurbplan.2019.103611&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.landurbplan.2019.103611&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Elliott L. R., White M. P., Sarran, C., Grellier, J., Garrett, J. K., Scoccimarro, E., &amp;amp; Fleming, L. E. (2019). The effects of meteorological conditions and daylight on nature-based recreational physical activity in England. Urban Forestry &amp;amp; Urban Greening, 42, 39-50. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.ufug.2019.05.005&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.ufug.2019.05.005&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;2018&#34;&gt;2018&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Garrett, J. K., White, M. P., Huang, J., Ng, S., Hui, Z., Leung, C., Tse, L.A., Fung, F., Elliott, L.R., Depledge, M.H. &amp;amp; Wong, M.C. (2018). Urban blue space and health and wellbeing in Hong Kong: Results from a survey of older adults. Health &amp;amp; Place, 55, 100-110. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.healthplace.2018.11.003&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.healthplace.2018.11.003&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Elliott, L. R., White, M. P., Grellier, J., Rees, S. E., Waters, R. D., &amp;amp; Fleming, L. E. (2018). Recreational visits to marine and coastal environments in England: Where, what, who, why, and when? Marine Policy, 97, 305-314. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.marpol.2018.03.013&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.marpol.2018.03.013&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;White, M. P., Elliott, L. R., Wheeler, B. W., &amp;amp; Fleming, L. E. (2018). Neighbourhood greenspace is related to physical activity in England, but only for dog owners. Landscape and Urban Planning, 174, 18–23. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.landurbplan.2018.01.004&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.landurbplan.2018.01.004&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;2017&#34;&gt;2017&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Grellier, J., White, M. P., Albin, M., Bell, S., Elliott, L. R., Gascón, M., Gualdi, S., Mancini, L., Nieuwenhuijsen, M.J., Sarigiannis, D.A. and Van Den Bosch, M. (2017). BlueHealth: a study programme protocol for mapping and quantifying the potential benefits to public health and well-being from Europe’s blue spaces. BMJ Open, 7(6), e016188. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1136/bmjopen-2017-016188&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1136/bmjopen-2017-016188&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Calogiuri, G., &amp;amp; Elliott, L. R. (2017). Why Do People Exercise in Natural Environments? Norwegian Adults’ Motives for Nature-, Gym-, and Sports-Based Exercise. International Journal of Environmental Research and Public Health, 14(4), 377. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.3390/ijerph14040377&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.3390/ijerph14040377&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;2016&#34;&gt;2016&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Elliott, L. R., White, M. P., Taylor, A. H., &amp;amp; Abraham, C. (2016). How do brochures encourage walking in natural environments in the UK? A content analysis. Health Promotion International, 33(2), 299–310. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1093/heapro/daw083&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1093/heapro/daw083&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-&lt;a href=&#34;https://lewis-r-elliott.github.io/Elliott_et_al_2016.pdf&#34;&gt;Published article&lt;/a&gt;
-&lt;a href=&#34;https://lewis-r-elliott.github.io/Elliott_et_al_2016_supps.zip&#34;&gt;Supplementary materials&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;White, M. P., Elliott, L. R., Taylor, T., Wheeler, B. W., Spencer, A., Bone, A., Depledge, M. H. and Fleming, L. E. (2016). Recreational physical activity in natural environments and implications for health: A population based cross-sectional study in England. Preventive Medicine, 91, 383–388. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.ypmed.2016.08.023&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.ypmed.2016.08.023&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-&lt;a href=&#34;https://lewis-r-elliott.github.io/White_et_al_2016.pdf&#34;&gt;Published article&lt;/a&gt;
-&lt;a href=&#34;https://lewis-r-elliott.github.io/White_et_al_2016_supps.docx&#34;&gt;Supplementary materials&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Frühauf, A., Niedermeier, M., Elliott, L. R., Ledochowski, L., Marksteiner, J., &amp;amp; Kopp, M. (2016). Acute effects of outdoor physical activity on affect and psychological well-being in depressed patients – A preliminary study. Mental Health and Physical Activity, 10, 4–9. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.mhpa.2016.02.002&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.mhpa.2016.02.002&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-&lt;a href=&#34;https://lewis-r-elliott.github.io/Fr%C3%BChauf_et_al_2016.pdf&#34;&gt;Published article&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;2015&#34;&gt;2015&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Elliott, L. R., White, M. P., Taylor, A. H., &amp;amp; Herbert, S. (2015). Energy expenditure on recreational visits to different natural environments. Social Science &amp;amp; Medicine, 139, 53–60. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.socscimed.2015.06.038&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.socscimed.2015.06.038&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://lewis-r-elliott.github.io/Elliott_et_al_2015.pdf&#34;&gt;Published article&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://lewis-r-elliott.github.io/Elliott_et_al_2015_supps.docx&#34;&gt;Supplementary materials&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://lewis-r-elliott.github.io/Elliott_et_al_2015_responses_1.docx&#34;&gt;Peer reviews and responses&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lewis Elliott PhD MSc BSc</title>
      <link>https://lewis-r-elliott.github.io/posts/homepage/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lewis-r-elliott.github.io/posts/homepage/</guid>
      <description>Hi. I built this website to consolidate and better organise my academic work than I thought was possible with pre-existing platforms like ResearchGate or Google Scholar. I also aim to (gradually) my work more &amp;lsquo;open&amp;rsquo; by including published papers as well as their draft versions, revisions, and peer reviews/responses, along with (where possible) related data and code.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;Hi. I built this website to consolidate and better organise my academic work than I thought was possible with pre-existing platforms like ResearchGate or Google Scholar. I also aim to (gradually) my work more &amp;lsquo;open&amp;rsquo; by including published papers as well as their draft versions, revisions, and peer reviews/responses, along with (where possible) related data and code.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
